inszoom.com 2016-12-08

# INSZoom Privacy Policy | Information Security

This privacy policy applies to the use of inszoom.com. At inszoom.com we recognize that privacy is important. This privacy policy applies to all of the services offered by inszoom.com. Our services require you to provide personal information to us in order to provide our full range of services. We highly value your privacy and make this policy easily available throughout our site to assist you in understanding the handling of information in the course of using this site.

### Log Files and Cookies

This website utilizes industry standard analytics packages which gathers limited information on visitors to our website automatically, and stores this anonymous information in server log files. This information may include IP addresses, browser type, basic IP information, referring pages, operating system used and date/time stamps. This information does not identify individual users; it is used only for site administration, as well as for analysis of website usage and trends. Additionally, cookies may be used to provide easier and faster access to website features such as logins and/or repeat visits. Cookies are very small text files that are stored on personal computers for reference purposes. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you have submitted while on our site. We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. A session cookie expires when your browser is closed, and a persistent cookie may stay on your hard drive for an extended period. Session cookies make it easier for you to navigate our site; persistent cookies can perform such activities as storing your password for forums or blogs so you do not have to sign in every time you visit those areas, and/or may be used to enable us to track and target the interests of our users so as to enhance the overall experience of using our site. We have no access to or administration abilities over any cookies that are used by any advertisers on our site.

This website may contain links to other sites that are not controlled in any way by us. Please be aware of this when you click on any such links; we are not responsible for the privacy practices and/or policies of any website other than our own. Consequently, we strongly suggest that you review the privacy policy of every website you visit, whether or not they are linked to by our own site.

### Registration and Use of Personal Information

Registration is not required in order to use or access this website. However, this site may make forums, blogs, message boards or similar available to its users. You may be required to register for these features, particularly if you wish to leave comments or provide articles.

If you do register, and in the process provide us with personally identifiable information, rest assured that any such information you provide will not be shared with any third-party organization except with your express consent.

Please note that if you post comments or articles to any forum, blog or message board on this site, any personally identifiable information you provide in those comments or articles may be read, collated and used by anyone viewing them. As such, we are not responsible for personally identifiable information you may choose to make available through these channels.

We also provide visitors to our website the opportunity to opt-in to receive communications from us. In this case, we ask the visitor for his or her email address and name. These communications will include our regular newsletter, product promotions and any other information that we feel may be pertinent to the visitor. You may opt out of receiving any, or all, of these communications by completing our feedback form, by clicking on the ‘unsubscribe’ link in any email we send to you, or by replying to any email we send you and entering the word UNSUBSCRIBE in the subject line.

Again, if you provide us with your email address and/or name for the purposes of receiving communications from us, this information will not be shared with any third-party organization except with your express consent.

### Access to Personally Identifiable Information

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer wish us to possess your information, you may request correction, updating, or deletion of your information by contacting completing our feedback form. You also may make your request by phone or postal mail at the address/phone number indicated at the end of this privacy policy.

### Security

We follow accepted industry standards to protect any personal information you have provided to us. However, please be aware that no method of electronic storage can ever be 100% secure. Therefore – as is the case with any organization – we are not in a position to guarantee the absolute security of your information.

INSZoom complies with the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework and the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries and Switzerland. INSZoom has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view INSZoom’s certification, please visit http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/

At INSZoom.com we recognize that privacy is important. This Privacy Policy applies to all of the products and services offered by INSZoom.com.

You may submit any questions you may have about our security procedures by completing our feedback form.

### Links to Other Websites

This website may contain links to other sites that are not controlled in any way by us. Please be aware of this when you click on any such links; we are not responsible for the privacy practices and/or policies of any website other than our own. Consequently, we strongly suggest that you review the privacy policy of every website you visit, whether or not they are linked to by our own site.

### Legal Disclaimer

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order or legal process served on our website.

## INSZoom App Privacy Policy

Welcome to the INSZoom App! The INSZoom App (“ **the App** ”, “ **we** ”, “ **us** ”, or “ **our** ”) is operated by INSZoom.com, Inc. (a Delaware corporation), which also operates the underlying case management application (“ **global.inszoom.com** ” or “ **Web Application** ”). The INSZoom App is designed for Users (“ **you** ”, “ **your** ”) to securely communicate with legal professionals or internal staff, store immigration related information for clients, and access or share immigration information anytime and from any location as well as a number of related services (collectively, with the App, the “ **Services** “).

For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, “ **Personal Information** ” means any information relating to a natural person that is or can be identified, directly or indirectly, by reference to an identification number (e.g., social security number, passport number) or one or several elements that characterize or allow someone to contact such person (e.g., address, phone number or email address), as well as any other non-public information about such person that is associated with or linked to any of the foregoing information.

**What does Personal Information include?**

Personal Information as related to the App can be:

– _Registration Personal Information_ : the username and password (or email address) you provide when you access and register for the INSZoom App; and/or,

– _Authentication Personal Information_ : Device identifiers, connection logs, or the username and password associated with your underlying account to access our Web Application at global.inszoom.com.

When you use the Services, and in particular when you install and use the INSZoom App, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and the collection, processing, use, and disclosure by INSZoom App and its service providers, of the Personal Information that you enter into the INSZoom App.

**For what purpose does the INSZoom App process your Personal Information?**

INSZoom App processes your Personal Information only in order to:

– Communicate with you, in connection with the provision of the Services made available through the INSZoom App, as well as other similar services that could be provided to you by the INSZoom App or by the Web Application. For this purpose, INSZoom App only uses your Registration Personal Information; or,

– Authenticate (verify) that it is actually you who is using the App, for which purpose we only use the Authentication Personal Information.

**What Personal Information does INSZoom App process?**

If you enter your email address on the App or the Web Application, we will use it to communicate with you about our Services. For the purpose of using the INSZoom App , the only type of Personal Information that must be communicated to INSZoom App is the username (or email address) and password you provide upon registration. The entry of all other types of data is optional.

Examples of the types of information that you may enter into the INSZoom App include:

– Name, surname, current visa, expiration dates and nationality;

– Employment information, immigration information, or travel Information, and/or,

– Names and contact information of your current clients or prospective clients, internal firm members, and other professionals associated with your office or firm.

INSZoom App only has access to your Registration Personal Information and Authentication Personal Information, the last IP address, Operating System language, Operating System country, and INSZoom App application language of the last computer where you have been authenticated to INSZoom App.

**Does INSZoom App share the information it receives?**

INSZoom App may use service providers (such as its data hosting service provider) to process your Personal Information, but only in order for INSZoom App to be able to provide to you the Services, including those enabled by the INSZoom App. The App does not share your Personal Information with any third party other than as described in this Privacy Policy. Each and every one of our service providers is contractually bound to protect the confidentiality of your Personal Information. If another company acquires our company, business, or our assets (including via bankruptcy), that company will possess the Personal Information collected by us and will assume the rights and obligations regarding your Personal Information as described in this Privacy Policy.

Regardless of any choices you make regarding your Personal Information, INSZoom App may disclose your Registration Personal Information and Authentication Personal Information if it believes in good faith that such disclosures are necessary: (a) to comply with relevant laws or to respond to subpoenas or warrants served on INSZoom App; (b) to protect or defend the rights or property of INSZoom App or other INSZoom App users; and/or (c) to investigate or assist in preventing any violation or potential violation of the law or this Privacy Policy.

**How secure is your Personal Information?**

The security of the Personal Information that you enter in the INSZoom App and the underlying Web Application is extremely important to us. This is why INSZoom App implements a variety of strong security measures, including advanced authentication measures and AES 256 bit encryption of data (except your Registration Personal Information and Authentication Personal Information) designed to prevent unauthorized access, alteration, and use.

**Server Security** ** **

All INSZoom App and Web Application data and servers are located in the United States. All our data communications are transmitted through Verisign’s 256-bit encryption technology. Our network and servers are protected by Cisco Networks Firewall, Check Point intrusion detection, software firewall and antivirus software. Information is only made available to authorized users. Servers and data storage are hosted with NTT America in an environment with 24×7 security and video surveillance monitored by security guards and protected by biometric hand scan entry systems and a mantrap controlled entrance/exit.

**ISO Certification**

INSZoom.com, Inc. is ISO certified. ISO 27001:2005 is the leading international standards for measuring information and Net security management systems. BSI’s audit of INSZoom’s security and quality management system measures includes analysis of the company’s management control, operating procedures, personnel, physical security, data transmission, infrastructure, vendors, systems maintenance, metrics and measurements, e-governance, BCP and Disaster recovery strategies, statutory and legal compliance and continuous improvements, through regular reviews and audits. This detailed process has strengthened set of standards for internal information and Net security management and company-wide processes for protecting information assets. Employees throughout the company’s worldwide offices have enhanced vision on the security awareness with client data integrity placed at the highest premium.

**U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework**

INSZoom.com, Inc. complies with the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework and the U.S-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries and Switzerland. INSZoom.com, Inc. has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement.

**Audit Review**

INSZoom.com, Inc. has selected the BIG 4 security specialist KPMG to carry out biannual review assessments of our products. The risk report is delivered to INSZoom.com, Inc. management at the end of the assessment, and INSZoom.com, Inc. closes all findings, if any, on product security measurements.

While INSZoom App has gone to great lengths to protect your Personal Information, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure; therefore, INSZoom App cannot guarantee its absolute security. In addition, the security of your Personal Information also depends on how you use the INSZoom App and Services and protect the username and password or email addresses that enable you to access your INSZoom App account or Web Application.

**How can you access and manage your Personal Information?**

You can access your Personal Information directly on the INSZoom App. For any questions or concerns you may have with respect to your Personal Information, you can contact: [support@INSZoom.com](mailto:support@INSZoom.com).

**Logs Data**

When you connect to the App from your device, we may send one or more cookies (small text files containing a string of characters) to your device. Such cookies are of two types: (i) cookies enabling us to offer you a better experience when using the App (Session ID cookies), and (ii) cookies enabling us to ensure that you have authorized the device you are using for the purpose of accessing your Personal Information on the App. These cookies are required for the use of the App. We do not use any other type of cookies.

Every time you visit the App as a registered user, INSZoom App also collects some information both directly and using third party services, such as cookies, your computer’s Internet Protocol (IP) address, requested pages or previously visited page. We use this information to improve your experience on the App and Web Applications.

**Revisions**

If you choose to use the INSZoom App, such use and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy is subject to occasional revision, and if we make any material changes in the way we use your Personal Information, we will notify you by sending you an email to the last email address you provided to us. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will be effective thirty (30) calendar days following our dispatch of an email notice to you. Please note that at all times you are responsible for updating your Personal Information to provide us with your most current email address or contact information. In the event that the last email address that you have provided us is not valid, or for any reason is not capable of delivering to you the notice described above, our dispatch of the email containing such notice will nonetheless constitute effective notice of the changes described in the notice. Continued use of the INSZoom App, following notice of such changes shall indicate your acknowledgement of such changes and agreement to be bound by the terms and conditions of such changes.

LAST UPDATED – July 13, 2015.

### Contact Details
